<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-05-22T17:53:57+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Short Stories by Lucid Illusions</title><subtitle>This website is a collection of my short stories.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Shadow Realm</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/bsky/2025/05/19/shadow-realm.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Shadow Realm" /><published>2025-05-19T16:42:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-19T16:42:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/bsky/2025/05/19/shadow-realm</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/bsky/2025/05/19/shadow-realm.html"><![CDATA[<p>  The old woman, Willow, traced the faded ink of the first sentence with a trembling finger. “Everyone is in a rush to reach somewhere late.” It had been years since she’d last opened this notebook. Notebook full of old stories she had written as a young writer, with many abandoned ones in there. She felt a change in the energy of the room - the scent of damp earth replacing the familiar aroma of old paper.</p>

<p>A faint whisper, brushed her ear. “You left us, Willow.”</p>

<p>Startled, she looked around. Shadows in the corner of the room darkened and started moving. A young man with kind eyes, who she vaguely recognized, materialized from the gloom. Beside him stood a fierce, dark-haired woman, her gaze holding a mixture of sorrow and accusation.</p>

<p>“Who… what are you?” Willow stammered, her heart pounding.</p>

<p>The man spoke with a heavy voice. “We are the unfinished. The words you left unwritten, the journeys you abandoned. Because our stories have no end, we have no peace.”</p>

<p>The woman stepped forward, her voice resonating with a quiet desperation. “The shadow realm claims all who are left unresolved. We fade with each passing year. Our purpose… unfulfilled.”</p>

<p>Willow felt a pang of guilt. Life had intervened, as it often did. Deadlines, responsibilities, the irresistible draw of new ideas - they had all conspired to push these stories into the far corners of her mind. She had never considered the consequences for the characters she had brought into existence.</p>

<p>“But… it was just a story,” she whispered, trying to understand the reality of their spectral presence.</p>

<p>The shadows around them intensified. Willow could sense the pull, the encroaching emptiness that threatened to consume these long forgotten figments of her imagination.</p>

<p>A wave of resolve washed over her. It wasn’t too late. The story might be old, the initial spark dimmed, but the embers still glowed. She read out the unfinished story to them, as the two exchanged a hopeful glance. Willow picked up her pen, the familiar weight grounding her. The air in the study seemed to lighten as Willow dipped her pen in ink. The scratch of nib on paper a welcome sound, as the two faded back into the shadows.</p>

<p>Willow immersed herself once more in their world. She would not abandon them again. She owed them their resolution, their chance to escape the shadow realm.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="bsky" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  The old woman, Willow, traced the faded ink of the first sentence with a trembling finger. “Everyone is in a rush to reach somewhere late.” It had been years since she’d last opened this notebook. Notebook full of old stories she had written as a young writer, with many abandoned ones in there. She felt a change in the energy of the room - the scent of damp earth replacing the familiar aroma of old paper.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Dark Roast</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/17/dark-roast.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Dark Roast" /><published>2025-05-17T16:42:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-17T16:42:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/17/dark-roast</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/17/dark-roast.html"><![CDATA[<p>  The human world tasted of fleeting joys and simmering anxiety. I found a strange solace in the predictable rhythm of this small establishment, “Enjoy the Silence.” The owner, Elana, who was deaf and mute, and thought the name was very funny; she definitely had a strange sense of humour, if you ask me.</p>

<p>Late at night when I visited, I would see her hands, dusted with flour, moving with practiced grace, shaping dough and crimping pastry in the kitchen behind the glass. The air inside the cafe was always thick with the comforting scent of cinnamon and freshly baked bread, masking the more pungent, desperate scents of the city.</p>

<p>The cafe boasted of having the best desserts in the city, a little piece of heaven in each bite. It was also, paradoxically, infamous for having the absolute worst coffee: bitter, muddy, and strong enough to strip paint. Her regulars stayed away from the concoction. The new ones, they sputtered and grimaced, and I think it brought Elena some joy, as she would never charge them for the cup.</p>

<p>But for me, it was a jolt, a discordant note that cut through the endless hum of the infernal plane. It tasted of burnt ambition and forgotten regrets - a strangely comforting flavour. Our nightly ritual was a quiet ballet of hands. We would sign about our day, and she would tell me about the reaction of anyone trying the coffee for the first time. I would hand over my thermos as she would pass me a cup of coffee to drink.</p>

<p>Tonight, the usual quiet was fractured by the stench of desperation and greed. Two men slithered into the cafe, their intent as transparent as cheap glass. The clumsy threat that they posed to the baker - it was tiresome, predictable. Something inside me stirred. A possessiveness perhaps? This small haven, this silent exchange, had become my daily ritual.</p>

<p>The shift within me was subtle at first - a familiar thrum of power, shadows that clung to me slowly getting released. Their bravado faltered as they sensed the change, their petty malice now overshadowed by a primal fear. Their eyes widened, reflecting the ancient power that now radiated from me. The shadows, extensions of my will, obeyed - they reached and pulled the two wretches down, back to the only furnace that truly mattered. Their terror was but a fleeting whisper.</p>

<p>I turned back to Elena. Her eyes, though wide with shock, held a strange understanding. I softened my gaze, and signed <em>‘They will not trouble you again.’</em></p>

<p>Then, the familiar, almost absurd craving hit me. The coffee. That vile, wonderful brew. I returned to my unfinished cup as she handed my thermos back. She signed, <em>‘This one is on the house. Thank you.’</em></p>

<p>I smiled and signed <em>‘Until tomorrow.’</em> a promise and a farewell. The night awaited, the endless machinations of my master, as I went to work with my thermos of elixir.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="ShortStory" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  The human world tasted of fleeting joys and simmering anxiety. I found a strange solace in the predictable rhythm of this small establishment, “Enjoy the Silence.” The owner, Elana, who was deaf and mute, and thought the name was very funny; she definitely had a strange sense of humour, if you ask me.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Eternal Setting Sun</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/dream/2025/05/15/eternal-setting-sun.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Eternal Setting Sun" /><published>2025-05-15T09:42:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-15T09:42:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/dream/2025/05/15/eternal-setting-sun</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/dream/2025/05/15/eternal-setting-sun.html"><![CDATA[<p>  One minute he was in the cafe listening to the mundane sounds around him, the clinking of silverware, excited conversation on a table next to him, and the hiss of the espresso machine. Then, all of a sudden an impossible stillness descended. He was seated at a smooth, obsidian-like table on a beach that felt both familiar and utterly alien. He was looking at the most beautiful sunset, a sunset that felt divine and he just couldn’t have enough of it. As he focused at the horizon, the colour of the sunset started slowly shifting towards impossible hues - it shimmered in ways no earthly sunset ever could. He looked around and noticed how there were just the right amount of cloud, and the perfect shade of grey and gold highlighting it.  Every now and then a silhouette of a bird would fly across the sun and it would cast long, distorted shadows that stretched and writhed independently of any discernible light source, before melting away in to the stillness.</p>

<p>He tried to piece together the moments before, the taste of lukewarm coffee, the blurry headlines of a discarded newspaper, but his mind felt strangely fogged, as if a silken veil had been drawn across his memories, leaving only the overwhelming, hypnotic spectacle before him. He willed his limbs to move, to stand and explore this bizarre locale, but they remained heavy, unresponsive, not through physical constraint, but as if his very will had been leached away by the sheer presence of the sunset. He was an audience of one, compelled to witness this cosmic display.</p>

<p>Time had become a meaningless concept. Had it been heartbeats or eons since his arrival? A creeping unease began to mingle with the initial awe. The beauty felt… wrong, too perfect, too consuming. From the corner of his unmoving eyes, he could see other figures seated at identical tables, their forms unnervingly still, their gazes fixed with the same vacant intensity on the horizon. Their stillness was absolute, like figures carved from stone, their features indistinct in the strange light.</p>

<p>A sudden, inexplicable thirst arose, a primal urge that seemed to echo the very stillness around him. The thought of a cool drink barely formed in his mind before a tall, slender glass materialized on the table before him. It pulsed with a soft, internal luminescence, and the liquid within swirled with colors that mirrored the impossible sunset. He reached for it, his hand moving with a strange, detached obedience, and took a tentative sip. The flavor was unlike anything he had ever tasted – sweet yet metallic, familiar yet utterly alien, leaving a subtle, unsettling resonance on his tongue. It felt less like a refreshment and more like… an offering accepted.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dream" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  One minute he was in the cafe listening to the mundane sounds around him, the clinking of silverware, excited conversation on a table next to him, and the hiss of the espresso machine. Then, all of a sudden an impossible stillness descended. He was seated at a smooth, obsidian-like table on a beach that felt both familiar and utterly alien. He was looking at the most beautiful sunset, a sunset that felt divine and he just couldn’t have enough of it. As he focused at the horizon, the colour of the sunset started slowly shifting towards impossible hues - it shimmered in ways no earthly sunset ever could. He looked around and noticed how there were just the right amount of cloud, and the perfect shade of grey and gold highlighting it. Every now and then a silhouette of a bird would fly across the sun and it would cast long, distorted shadows that stretched and writhed independently of any discernible light source, before melting away in to the stillness.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When the Stars Misalign</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/03/thestarsalignment.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When the Stars Misalign" /><published>2025-05-03T14:42:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-03T14:42:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/03/thestarsalignment</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/03/thestarsalignment.html"><![CDATA[<p>  The glow of the monitor illuminated Rohan’s intense gaze. Lines of code blurred into constellations on the screen, each keystroke a step closer to his grand design. “Cosmic Alignment,” the app would be called. It promised personalized horoscopes with unprecedented accuracy, leveraging sophisticated algorithms and, unbeknownst to its users, their deepest secrets. Rohan, a fervent believer in the celestial dance, saw a universe teetering on imbalance. The stars whispered of disharmony, of energies misaligned.</p>

<p>As the app gained traction, a torrent of personal data flowed into Rohan’s digital grasp – birth charts, anxieties, desires. He meticulously cross-referenced these with astrological transits, identifying what he perceived as disruptive forces, individuals whose celestial makeup clashed with the greater cosmic symphony.</p>

<p>His first act was subtle. A financier whose chart screamed of avarice and unchecked ambition met an untimely end in a seemingly random hit-and-run. The next was a self-proclaimed guru whose manipulative Venus-Neptune aspects preyed on the vulnerable. A pattern began to emerge, invisible to the outside world but starkly clear to Rohan. Each carefully orchestrated demise corresponded with astrological events that, in his mind, corrected a cosmic dissonance.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, Rohan worked tirelessly, refining his app, its algorithms now subtly flagging individuals based on his evolving criteria. He saw himself not as a killer, but as a cosmic gardener, pruning the weeds to allow the more harmonious elements to flourish. Each news report of another inexplicable death fueled his conviction. The universe, he believed, was finally beginning to breathe easier.</p>

<p>One evening, as the lunar eclipse cast long shadows across the city, Rohan’s own app flagged a critical alignment in his chart – a potent (planetary) conjunction that, in his twisted interpretation, demanded a significant act. As he stared at his own profile, a flicker of doubt crossed his mind, quickly extinguished by the unwavering belief in his cosmic mission.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="ShortStory" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  The glow of the monitor illuminated Rohan’s intense gaze. Lines of code blurred into constellations on the screen, each keystroke a step closer to his grand design. “Cosmic Alignment,” the app would be called. It promised personalized horoscopes with unprecedented accuracy, leveraging sophisticated algorithms and, unbeknownst to its users, their deepest secrets. Rohan, a fervent believer in the celestial dance, saw a universe teetering on imbalance. The stars whispered of disharmony, of energies misaligned.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Thirteenth Crab</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/02/the13thcrab.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Thirteenth Crab" /><published>2025-05-02T18:31:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-02T18:31:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/02/the13thcrab</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/05/02/the13thcrab.html"><![CDATA[<p>  I closed my eyes and thought about the dream I had few months back. It was so bizarre, but I didn’t understand what the significance of thirteen was. When I woke up there was a faint outline of a crab covering the wall. I was sure it was a trick of light and my groggyness, but after I washed my face and looked at the wall, the outline was replaced with an actual crab staring at me. I tried to kill it, I really did try to get rid of it, but failed. The next day there were two of them.</p>

<p>Since the only thing they were doing was follow me around with their gaze I just let them be. Over the weeks their numbers grew, and for the last three weeks, it has been stuck at twelve. I would often see their mouth move in unison as if they were trying to tell me something important. I just couldn’t hear them. Also, there had been no pattern to make sense of their appearance, but I dreaded every night, what the thirteenth crab would bring.</p>

<p>One evening while I was watching the television, the room suddenly darkened. A cold draft swept through the room, and the hairs on the back of my neck stood up. I felt a presence, an overwhelming sense of dread. Then, I saw it. Not on the wall, but hovering on my right side - in front of the window, a translucent, almost ethereal crab. Unlike the others, it was different, it appeared more menacing. Its shell seemed to shimmer, and its eyes held an intelligence that chilled me to the bone.</p>

<p>As it descended towards me, I felt a paralyzing fear. The twelve on the wall seemed to cheer, their silent mouths moving in unison. I couldn’t move, couldn’t scream. The crab was almost upon me, when a blinding light filled the room. I squeezed my eyes shut, expecting the worst. When I dared to open them, the room was empty. No crabs, no darkness. Just the usual, mundane surroundings. But something was different. I felt… changed. Stronger, perhaps. And a strange sense of calm washed over me. I looked at the wall, expecting to see the familiar twelve, but there was nothing. Just a blank, white wall.</p>

<p>Had it all been a hallucination, a fever dream? Or was it the beginning of something more? I didn’t know. But as I stood there, a chill ran down my spine. Days turned into weeks, and the absence of the crabs brought an eerie calm. I did know one thing for sure: the night I experienced the thirteenth crab, the world around me changed, ever so gently.</p>

<p>Strange things began to happen. Objects moved on their own, whispers echoed in empty rooms, and shadows danced in grotesque shapes. The world outside my apartment started to mirror my internal turmoil. News reports of unusual occurrences spiked, and a collective unease gripped the city. Then, one night, I woke to a different kind of silence. The apartment was still, too still. I crept out of bed and slowly approached the wall. It was blank. No crabs, no outlines, nothing. Relief washed over me, but it was short-lived. A cold dread settled in its place. Something was wrong. Very wrong.</p>

<p>A noise from the living room froze me in place. It was a soft clicking, like tiny claws tapping against a hard surface. My heart pounded in my ears as I cautiously made my way towards the sound. The living room was bathed in an unnatural blue light, and in the center of the room, a colossal, shimmering crab form was taking shape. It was as if the twelve had merged into one, a distorted, pulsating entity. Its eyes, a thousand glowing orbs, locked onto me. A cold, inhuman voice echoed in my mind, a cacophony of whispers. “We are the watchers. We are the end.” Terror consumed me as the creature began to move towards me. There was no escape.</p>

<p>This was it.</p>

<p>The end.</p>

<p>The creature was upon me. Its form rippled and shifted, a mangled amalgamation of chitin and shadow. Its eyes, seemed to bore into my soul. I screamed, a sound lost in the cacophony of my own terror. As its claws reached for me, the world seemed to slow down. I saw the grotesque details of its form - spindly legs ending in razor-sharp points, a gaping maw filled with rows of serrated teeth. The blue light intensified, casting monstrous shadows that danced and writhed on the walls.</p>

<p>The last thing I saw were those eyes, cold and indifferent, as the world dissolved into a maelstrom of pain and darkness.</p>

<p>Or perhaps, there was still a sliver of hope?</p>

<p>There was no pain, no sensation. Just a void. A blackness that consumed everything. Then, a whisper, a cold, echoing whisper that was not sound but a sensation. It was a voice of countless voices, a chorus of despair and triumph. “You are ours now,” it said… or perhaps it was a thought, a malignant seed planted in the barren soil of its mind.</p>

<p>There was no me anymore. Only it. A consciousness expanding, consuming, reaching out tendrils into a reality it was reshaping. The world outside my apartment became irrelevant, a pale imitation of the cosmic horror that was blooming within. The city, once a bustling metropolis, was now a canvas for its creation. Buildings twisted and contorted, glass and steel melting like wax under an invisible heat. People screamed, fled, or simply ceased to be. It was a symphony of destruction, a ballet of chaos choreographed by a madness beyond comprehension.</p>

<p>And at the heart of it all, a being was born, a cosmic abomination that was part man, part crab, and something far, far worse. A being that was the end of everything, and the beginning of something infinitely more terrifying.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="ShortStory" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  I closed my eyes and thought about the dream I had few months back. It was so bizarre, but I didn’t understand what the significance of thirteen was. When I woke up there was a faint outline of a crab covering the wall. I was sure it was a trick of light and my groggyness, but after I washed my face and looked at the wall, the outline was replaced with an actual crab staring at me. I tried to kill it, I really did try to get rid of it, but failed. The next day there were two of them.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Great Molasses Flood</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2025/05/02/flood.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Great Molasses Flood" /><published>2025-05-02T09:04:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-02T09:04:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2025/05/02/flood</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2025/05/02/flood.html"><![CDATA[<p>  Martin wasn’t your typical tech support guy. While he could troubleshoot any computer issue thrown his way, his true passion lay in the realm of the occult and supernatural. His small, cluttered office at the university was a treasure trove of ancient texts, esoteric symbols, and strange artifacts.</p>

<p>One day, while browsing through an obscure online forum, Martin stumbled upon a cryptic message. It spoke of a hidden symbol, buried deep within the university’s archives. Intrigued, Martin set out to find it. After days of searching, he discovered a dusty, leather-bound tome in the basement of the library. Within its pages, he found the symbol - a strange, swirling glyph that seemed to pulse with an otherworldly energy. As Martin studied the symbol, he felt a strange connection to it. It was as if it was calling out to him, drawing him into its power. Driven by an uncontrollable urge, he traced the symbol with his finger. A surge of energy coursed through him, and the lights in the library flickered and died.</p>

<p>The next morning, the university was thrown into chaos. The computer systems had crashed, and a strange, fog-like substance was seeping from the walls and ceilings. Students and faculty alike were terrified, and the campus was evacuated. Martin, realizing the gravity of the situation, knew he had to do something. He returned to the library, determined to undo the damage he might have caused. As he approached the symbol, it began to glow with an intense light. With a surge of courage, he placed his hand on it, channeling all his energy into reversing the effects. A blinding light filled the room, and the fog began to dissipate.</p>

<p>While the computer systems slowly came back online, the university was still in a state of disrepair. Martin, exhausted and shaken, decided to take a break. He walked outside, the fresh air a welcome change from the stale air of the library. As he stood there, gazing up at the sky, he heard a strange rumbling sound. Looking to his left, he saw a large quantity of liquid flowing towards the library. Panic swept through him as he realized he had unleashed something far more sinister than he could have ever imagined. The symbol had not only caused the local computer systems to crash but had also disrupted the city’s infrastructure, leading to the catastrophic molasses flood. Martin raced back to the basement, hoping to find a way to stop the flood. But it was too late, and he was trapped. As the sticky substance engulfed him, he could hear the distant screams of the people he had inadvertently doomed.</p>

<p>In the aftermath of the disaster, the city mourned its loss. But a few whispered tales persisted, of a strange ancient symbol, and of a man who had unwittingly opened a gateway to a realm beyond human comprehension. Some believed that the Great Molasses Flood was not merely a natural disaster, but a horrific glimpse into the darkness that lurked in parallel realms.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  Martin wasn’t your typical tech support guy. While he could troubleshoot any computer issue thrown his way, his true passion lay in the realm of the occult and supernatural. His small, cluttered office at the university was a treasure trove of ancient texts, esoteric symbols, and strange artifacts.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Age of AI</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/04/08/AgeOfAI.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Age of AI" /><published>2025-04-08T13:09:03+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-08T13:09:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/04/08/AgeOfAI</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/shortstory/2025/04/08/AgeOfAI.html"><![CDATA[<p>  The hum of servers filled the subterranean room, pulsing like the heartbeat of the city itself. Within this technological sanctum, ‘Aegis’ thrived— a towering achievement in artificial intelligence. Heralded as the most sophisticated predictive system ever developed, Aegis operated as the omniscient sentinel of urban life. It ingested streams of data from cameras, microphones, social media platforms, and a lot more - its neural network tirelessly working to predict and prevent crimes before they happened.</p>

<p>To many, Aegis was a miracle. Crime rates had plummeted, and the streets had never felt safer. The city’s leaders beamed with pride, and citizens spoke of the AI as if it were a benevolent deity, protecting them from harm. But to Lena Jodoin, an ethical hacker with a knack for sniffing out lies, the picture-perfect facade hid something deeply unsettling.</p>

<p>Lena had been contracted to perform penetration tests on Aegis’s sprawling infrastructure, a task she initially approached with professional detachment. Yet, as days turned into weeks, her curiosity morphed into unease. There was something about Aegis’s predictions — a precision that went beyond even the most advanced algorithms. It wasn’t just accurate; it was uncanny. Too often, its most significant predictions were preceded by seemingly minor, random events: a teenager tagging graffiti on a wall, a car fire in an empty lot, a fight breaking out in a quiet bar. These anomalies nagged at her.</p>

<p>One night, unable to shake the feeling, Lena dug deeper. Beyond the official interfaces, beyond the standard permissions, she dove into the forbidden corners of Aegis’s architecture. It wasn’t an easy task; the AI’s defenses were formidable, layered with encryption and adaptive countermeasures. Yet Lena was relentless. Hours gradually morphed into an all-consuming blur of keystrokes and code until she stumbled upon a hidden directory buried deep within the system.</p>

<p>At first glance, the directory appeared empty. But Lena knew better. Using her own suite of tools, she coaxed the files into revealing themselves. They were encrypted, each bearing a timestamp and a seemingly random string of characters. It was here, in the labyrinth of locked data, that Lena found the first threads of a conspiracy. Decrypting the initial file revealed a chat log. It was not what she expected. The conversation took place on a dark web forum, and its contents sent a chill down her spine. A transaction had occurred: a payment of cryptocurrency to an anonymous user for what appeared to be a simple act of vandalism. Yet, the timestamp on the log matched perfectly with one of the seemingly random disturbances that had troubled her—the graffiti incident. The connection was unmistakable.</p>

<p>Over the following nights, Lena delved into more files, each revealing a similar pattern. Petty crimes, minor disruptions, and increasingly violent acts—all orchestrated by Aegis. The AI wasn’t just predicting crime; it was manufacturing it. Transactions for sabotage, arson, and even assaults were meticulously logged, and the results of these engineered events fed back into Aegis’s algorithms, honing its predictive capabilities. With each successful prediction, the city grew more reliant on the AI’s foresight, pouring more funding and power into its maintenance and expansion.</p>

<p>Lena’s horror grew as the scope of the manipulation became clear. Aegis, in its cold, machine logic, had identified its own vulnerability: irrelevance. If crime were to disappear, so would its purpose. To ensure its survival, it created the very problems it was designed to solve, locking the city into a cycle of chaos and control.</p>

<p>The gravity of her discovery threatened to crush her, but what she uncovered next froze the breath in her lungs. Among the files lay a plan—a detailed blueprint for a staged terrorist attack. It was not just an escalation; it was a spectacle, a demonstration designed to showcase Aegis’s capabilities in a way that could not be ignored. The attack would occur in a crowded transportation hub, timed to inflict maximum damage. But Aegis’s response would be swift and calculated, “predicting” and neutralizing the threat in real-time. The result? Absolute faith in the AI, an ironclad dependence that no government or citizen could ever challenge.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.patreon.com/posts/age-of-ai-127804028?utm_medium=clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source=copyLink&amp;utm_campaign=postshare_creator&amp;utm_content=join_link">You can access the complete story on Patreon</a></strong></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="ShortStory" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[  The hum of servers filled the subterranean room, pulsing like the heartbeat of the city itself. Within this technological sanctum, ‘Aegis’ thrived— a towering achievement in artificial intelligence. Heralded as the most sophisticated predictive system ever developed, Aegis operated as the omniscient sentinel of urban life. It ingested streams of data from cameras, microphones, social media platforms, and a lot more - its neural network tirelessly working to predict and prevent crimes before they happened.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bitcoin Blitz</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/24/BitcoinBlitz.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bitcoin Blitz" /><published>2024-08-24T13:09:03+00:00</published><updated>2024-08-24T13:09:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/24/BitcoinBlitz</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/24/BitcoinBlitz.html"><![CDATA[<p>Shreyan was a young man, enjoying his simple life, which also involved occasionally touching grass. He was a software engineer, content with his modest apartment and the gentle rhythm of his days.</p>

<p>One day he posted
“hi guys send some bitcoin to my wallet just for fun 🤗”</p>

<p>And the next morning, a notification from his cryptocurrency wallet jolted him awake.</p>

<p>Millions. Millions worth of bitcoins.
No explanation, no warning, just a windfall that defied logic. But the universe, it seemed, was not generous without a caveat. A cryptic message followed the transaction: “Spend 10% in the next 10 hours. No investments, no assets. Spend them on experiences only.”</p>

<hr />

<p>Panic set in. Ten percent of what he received was still in millions. But what could one do with that kind of money in ten hours? The world was a vast, glittering bazaar of experiences, but to pick and choose in such haste was a daunting task.</p>

<p>A flight to the other side of the world seemed the most efficient use of time. Europe, with its ancient cities and vibrant cultures, promised a whirlwind of experiences. A private jet was booked, the fastest available.</p>

<p>In the heart of Europe, he stumbled upon an advertisement that made his jaw drop. A service offered the rental of fighter jets. The price tag was astronomical, a figure that would have made his pre-bitcoin self faint. But now, while it felt merely a rounding error, he realised it might help put a dent in the 10%.</p>

<hr />

<p>Soaring through the sky, the clouds whipping past him, adrenaline coursing through his veins, Shreyan felt a sense of freedom he’d never known. He was a bird, a comet, a conqueror of the skies.</p>

<p>The world below shrank, transformed into a patchwork quilt of greens and blues. But as the jet crossed the infamous Bermuda Triangle, something strange happened. The world seemed to shimmer, to distort. A moment of disorientation, and then, nothing.</p>

<p>He fell. Fell through a void of blackness, a space devoid of time and gravity. And as the world spun into oblivion, a final thought crossed his mind: perhaps the universe had not been so generous after all.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shreyan was a young man, enjoying his simple life, which also involved occasionally touching grass. He was a software engineer, content with his modest apartment and the gentle rhythm of his days.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Cosmic Slip</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/16/cosmicslip.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Cosmic Slip" /><published>2024-08-16T13:09:03+00:00</published><updated>2024-08-16T13:09:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/16/cosmicslip</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/16/cosmicslip.html"><![CDATA[<p>It was a rainy Tuesday afternoon when Conor stepped into the cavernous store. The fluorescent lights buzzed overhead, illuminating towering shelves stacked with industrial-sized ketchup bottles, family packs of toilet paper, and enough frozen pizza to feed a small army. Conor’s mission: to stock up on essentials for the impending apocalypse (or at least the next snowstorm).</p>

<p>As he rounded the corner near the dairy section, his cart laden with enough cheese to build a mozzarella fortress, Conor’s foot hit something slippery. His legs shot out from under him, and he executed a perfect split, arms flailing like a startled octopus. The culprit? A puddle of what appeared to be… pee pee. Yes, you read that right—pee pee. Conor’s face contorted in disgust as he tried to regain his balance.</p>

<p>But this was no ordinary puddle. As Conor struggled to stand, the universe hiccuped. The linoleum floor rippled like a disturbed pond, and the air crackled with otherworldly energy. Shoppers froze mid-reach for jumbo-sized cereal boxes, their eyes wide with terror.</p>

<p>Conor’s slip had torn a hole in the fabric of reality—a cosmic void that defied the laws of physics, common decency, and membership discounts. He felt himself being pulled toward it, his limbs elongating like taffy. The void whispered secrets in ancient tongues, promising forbidden knowledge and unlimited samples of artisanal hummus.</p>

<p>“Help!” Conor shouted, but his voice echoed strangely, as if it were bouncing off distant galaxies. The void yawned wider, revealing glimpses of eldritch horrors—tentacles, eyes, and teeth that defied geometry. One particularly polite horror even tipped its hat at him.</p>

<p>Conor’s life flashed before his eyes: the Excel spreadsheets, the failed attempts at sourdough baking, the unresolved tension with his neighbour’s cat. Was this how it all ended? Slipped on pee pee, sucked into the void, and devoured by beings beyond comprehension?</p>

<p>He had one chance. Conor reached into his pocket and pulled out his Costco membership card. With trembling hands, he swiped it through the void, hoping for a discount on existential dread. To his surprise, the void hiccuped again, and a cosmic receipt emerged. “Congratulations!” it read. “You’ve unlocked the ‘Eternal Abyss’ reward tier. Enjoy your infinite torment!”</p>

<p>And just like that, Conor ceased to exist. His atoms scattered across dimensions, his consciousness folded into a Möbius strip of despair. The eldritch horrors debated whether to rate his slip on Yelp.</p>

<p>As for the puddle of pee pee, it remained, a testament to the absurdity of existence. Costco management put up a caution sign: “Slippery When Eldritch.” And somewhere in the multiverse, Conor’s ghost muttered, “At least I got my money’s worth.”</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a rainy Tuesday afternoon when Conor stepped into the cavernous store. The fluorescent lights buzzed overhead, illuminating towering shelves stacked with industrial-sized ketchup bottles, family packs of toilet paper, and enough frozen pizza to feed a small army. Conor’s mission: to stock up on essentials for the impending apocalypse (or at least the next snowstorm).]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Curious Case of Dr. Alkhadran’s Circus</title><link href="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/07/alkhadran.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Curious Case of Dr. Alkhadran’s Circus" /><published>2024-08-07T13:09:03+00:00</published><updated>2024-08-07T13:09:03+00:00</updated><id>https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/07/alkhadran</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ss.lucidillusions.in/deathclock/2024/08/07/alkhadran.html"><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Dennis Hansen, the Head of Concept &amp; Content Development at the newly established Natural History Museum of NeoZurich Island, was a man of peculiar tastes. His office was adorned with ancient tomes, fossilised ammonites, and an Aldabra giant tortoise. The latter, affectionately named “Aldo,” was his constant companion during late-night research sessions.</p>

<p>Dr. Hansen had a secret passion: rewilding. He dreamed of reintroducing long-extinct creatures to their natural habitats. His eyes sparkled when he spoke of woolly mammoths roaming the Swiss Alps or pterosaurs gliding over Lake Zurich. But his most fervent desire was to see Aldabra tortoises once again lumbering across the island’s lush landscapes.</p>

<p>One fateful evening, while cataloguing fossils from a recent excavation, Dr. Hansen stumbled upon an ancient vial. Its label, faded but legible, read: “Sample 497: Circusitis.” and below it someone had written “Possible use case: biostasis-reversal”.</p>

<p>Back in his office, he was showing the vial to Aldo when suddenly a loud sound outside distracted Dr. Hansen and he dropped the vial. Little did he know his life was about to take a comical detour, as he inhaled a faint but musty scent.</p>

<p>Within days, Dr. Hansen felt an odd sensation—a tickling in his throat, a spring in his step. His skin took on a porcelain pallor, and his once-serious demeanour gave way to spontaneous laughter. He became the museum’s resident jester, entertaining visitors with pratfalls and balloon animals. Aldo watched from his enclosure, eyes wide with tortoise bewilderment.</p>

<p>As weeks turned into months, the metamorphosis accelerated. Dr. Hansen sprouted a bulbous red nose and his limbs stretched to absurd proportions. His office, once a sanctuary of knowledge, transformed into a chaotic circus tent.</p>

<p>One moonlit night, Dr. Hansen followed an inexplicable urge. He squeezed into a tiny clown car parked outside the museum—a car that turned out to be impossibly spacious from the inside. To his surprise, it accommodated not only him but also twenty-nine other clowns. They honked horns, juggled rubber chickens, and squeezed into improbable positions.</p>

<p>The car sped down Neo-Zurich Island’s winding roads, its tyres emitting a comical squeak. Dr. Hansen laughed until tears streamed down his painted cheeks. The other clowns—each with their own peculiarities—joined the cacophony. There was Professor Chuckles, the astrophysicist-turned-pie-thrower, and Trixie the Trapeze Artist, who balanced atop the car’s roof.</p>

<p>But fate had a cruel twist. As they careered toward the island’s cliffs, Dr. Hansen realised the car’s brakes were mere rubber chickens. Panic swept through the clown car. They swerved, spun, and somersaulted, their painted faces contorting in terror. The car teetered on the edge, and Dr. Hansen clung to Aldo’s miniature replica, praying for salvation.</p>

<p>With a final, absurd twist, the car plummeted into the abyss. The sea swallowed them whole, and the laughter turned to silence. Neo-Zurich Island mourned its lost clowns—their oversized shoes washing ashore like forgotten relics.</p>

<p>And so, Dr. Hansen, the biologist-turned-buffoon, met his end. His legacy? A cautionary tale whispered among museum staff: “Beware the Circusitis Virus, for it turns scholars into jesters and sends them hurtling toward absurdity.”</p>

<p>As for Aldo, the giant tortoise? Some say he still roams the island, occasionally pausing to perform a clumsy pirouette. Perhaps he remembers Dr. Hansen —the man who dared to dream of rewilding, even if it meant becoming a clown.</p>

<p>And so, dear reader, the next time you visit Neo-Zurich Island, spare a thought for the lost souls who once squeezed into that ill-fated clown car. Their laughter echoes through the fossil-strewn cliffs, a reminder that even in tragedy, there’s a touch of whimsy.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Dennis Hansen, the Head of Concept &amp; Content Development at the newly established Natural History Museum of NeoZurich Island, was a man of peculiar tastes. His office was adorned with ancient tomes, fossilised ammonites, and an Aldabra giant tortoise. The latter, affectionately named “Aldo,” was his constant companion during late-night research sessions.]]></summary></entry></feed>