<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-19T18:29:22+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Short Stories</title><subtitle>This is a blog compiling all the stories from the prompts received on bluesky.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Reinvention</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/08/reinvention.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reinvention" /><published>2023-09-08T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-08T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/08/reinvention</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/08/reinvention.html"><![CDATA[<p>He was a loner, had no friends, always being bullied by everyone. He would go to sleep wishing he was someone else. Someone smarter, stronger, more attractive, and he felt all of these things would make him successful. He hated how mundane his life felt, the job bored him, his skills seemed mediocre. Everyday it seemed to him he is wasting his potential, trapped in a body and a mind that did not suit him.</p>

<p>When he came across the project, it was an easy choice for him to volunteer. The scientists promised him a chance to become a new person, with enhanced abilities and better personality. The science of genetic engineering and neural manipulation had reached its peak, and he felt this science could allow a way to rewrite not just their identity but help shape a new destiny.</p>

<p>He signed the consent form, without even reading the fine print, just eager to start his new life.</p>

<p>As he woke up groggily, he looked around the chamber. It was dark with mostly LED lights blinking back at him. He could faintly make the wires and tubes that were hooked on to him. He felt a sudden surge of pain in his head, as if something was trying to penetrate through his skull. He tried too scream - but no sound came out.</p>

<p>As his eyes got used to the low lit chamber, he saw other people in similar chambers. Their faces twisted in agony, some even had grotesque mutations like extra limbs, or eyes. Others had parts of their bodies missing, replaced with metal.</p>

<p>As he turned his head, he caught his reflection in a glass window. He recoiled in horror as he realized he was one of them, completely unrecognizable even to himself. His eyes were not bloodshot, but just red and somewhat flowing, his skin looked scaly and he opened his mouth to look at his sharp and jagged teeth. There were small bumps on his head and as he finally looked down, he saw claws instead of his hands and feet.</p>

<p>He was not human anymore.</p>

<p>He heard a voice in his head, cold and emotionless. “Good morning Subject 27, welcome to the reinvention program. You have been selected to be part of a new species. You’re now superior to humans in every way. You will undergo a series of tests to evaluate your performance and compatibility. If you succeed, you will join the elite ranks of the new world order. If you fail, you will be terminated.”</p>

<p>He felt a shock in his brain, making him convulse.</p>

<p>“Your first test begins now. Good luck.”</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[He was a loner, had no friends, always being bullied by everyone. He would go to sleep wishing he was someone else. Someone smarter, stronger, more attractive, and he felt all of these things would make him successful. He hated how mundane his life felt, the job bored him, his skills seemed mediocre. Everyday it seemed to him he is wasting his potential, trapped in a body and a mind that did not suit him.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Parking</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/06/parking.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Parking" /><published>2023-09-06T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-06T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/06/parking</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/06/parking.html"><![CDATA[<p>Certain workdays feel like they’ve been plucked straight from the depths of hell, and today happened to be one of those. It dragged on endlessly, sapping every ounce of my energy, and by the time I left, hunger gnawed at my insides. The rain, intensifying as I drove through the dark evening, made visibility a challenge. So, I made a spur-of-the-moment decision to pause for a quick bite. A swift search on my map app led me to a small dine-in place adjacent to a parking lot, and I decided to head there.</p>

<p>As I approached the parking lot, its sign, its neon light flickering erratically, struck me as oddly run-down for the location. The lot itself, as I pulled in, seemed nearly abandoned, with just a few cars haphazardly scattered about, casting eerie shadows in the dimly lit expanse. It had an undeniably sketchy feel to it, but the relentless rain convinced me to prioritize convenience over caution.</p>

<p>I selected a parking space close to the entrance and stepped out of my vehicle. The ticket booth was manned by a pale and dispassionate man who seemed utterly disinterested as I approached.</p>

<p>“Hello,” I greeted him. “What’s the rate for an hour?”</p>

<p>In reply, the man simply gestured toward a sign, upon which was inscribed, “Contribute what you can. No reimbursements. No grievances.”</p>

<p>The unusual policy struck me as odd, but I shrugged it off. Maybe he was having a bad day. Retrieving my wallet, I handed him a ten-dollar bill.</p>

<p>“Keep the change,” I offered with a faint attempt at friendliness.</p>

<p>The man accepted the money in silence, his gaze still fixed on the wall behind me. He handed me a ticket in return, never once making eye contact. An unsettling chill ran down my spine as I walked back to my car.</p>

<p>I couldn’t determine whether it was just in my head, but the parking lot seemed to have grown even darker, and the rain had intensified.</p>

<p>I also realized, with a growing unease, that there were no other exits except for the one through which I had entered.</p>

<p>Nervously, I settled into my car, locked the doors, and surveyed my surroundings. After a brief internal debate, my survival instinct prevailed, urging me to leave. I started the engine and inched toward the exit. I might have moved a few feet when I saw something move in the shadows. A monstrous, indistinct creature with writhing tentacles and multiple eyes slithered menacingly toward  the car, blocking my escape.</p>

<p>In sheer panic, I reacted, jamming my foot on the brake pedal and blaring my car horn, but the creature stood its ground, refusing to yield even an inch. Its numerous eyes remained fixated on me, as if anticipating something.</p>

<p>My gaze fell to the ticket I had received earlier, now clutched tightly in my trembling hand. In bold red ink, it read: “Welcome to the parking lot of madness. You have paid for an hour of horror. Enjoy your stay.”</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certain workdays feel like they’ve been plucked straight from the depths of hell, and today happened to be one of those. It dragged on endlessly, sapping every ounce of my energy, and by the time I left, hunger gnawed at my insides. The rain, intensifying as I drove through the dark evening, made visibility a challenge. So, I made a spur-of-the-moment decision to pause for a quick bite. A swift search on my map app led me to a small dine-in place adjacent to a parking lot, and I decided to head there.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Eldritch</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/05/eldritch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Eldritch" /><published>2023-09-05T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-05T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/05/eldritch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/05/eldritch.html"><![CDATA[<p>Amy loved crabs, she would read about them, draw them and would love going to the beach searching for them. It helped that her parents were Marine Biologists and would shift base every few years. She used to love going to search for crabs with her parents on Sundays. As she grew older, she would ride her bike to the beach and look for crabs and journal about them.</p>

<p>On her 16th Birthday, her parents told her they were moving to Japan for the next year, and she couldn’t believe it. She felt like one of her life long dreams just came true. Of all the crab species, one that held her fascination the most were the heikegani crabs.</p>

<p>These crabs were believed to bore the faces of ancient warriors on their shells. According to legend, they were the reincarnated spirits of the Heike clan, who perished in a naval battle against the Genji clan in the 12th century.</p>

<p>Amy wanted to collect the heikegani shells and study their patterns, hoping to find some clues to their mysterious origin.</p>

<p>The first few weeks after moving there were a whirlwind of getting used to the new life. She made a few friends at school who would tell her about the local legends. Stories from mythology and ghost stories. She would make notes from these stories as most of them were related to the Heiki clans. Her friends told her about sunken shipwrecks and how it were the ghosts of the Heiki who were responsible.</p>

<p>One Sunday, while her parents were out for work, she decided to go to the beach and search for crabs. She looked out the window, and the clear sky made her decide to go snorkeling near one of the many sunken shipwreck that was rumored to be haunted by the ghosts of the Heike.</p>

<p>She took her father’s boat and set off alone. She wanted to see the heikegani up close, and maybe even catch one for her collection.</p>

<p>She reached the wreck site and put on her mask and fins. With a graceful leap into the water, she embarked on her journey towards the sunken vessel, a shadowy silhouette resting on its side at the bottom of the sea. Schools of vibrant fish darted among the nooks and crannies, while corals and seaweed flourished on the rusted metal. She also saw dozens of heikegani crawling on the hull, their shells gleaming in the dim light.</p>

<p>She felt a surge of excitement and curiosity. She drew closer to one of the crabs, extending her hand to touch it. To her surprise, it did not scuttle away or nip at her fingers. Instead, it turned its head and looked at her with its beady eyes. She gasped, startled by the clarity of its face — it wasn’t a random arrangement of bumps and ridges but an uncanny likeness of a human visage. A face she recognized.</p>

<p>It was her father’s face.</p>

<p>She recoiled in horror and let go of the crab. She looked around and saw that all the other heikegani had similar faces. Faces of people she knew. Her mother, her brother, her friends, her neighbors. All staring at her with blank expressions.</p>

<p>She felt a cold hand grab her ankle and pull her down. She screamed and kicked, but it was too late. She was being dragged into the depths of the shipwreck, where more heikegani awaited her. She saw her own face as a heikegani swam past her.</p>

<p>She realized then that she had made a terrible mistake. The heikegani were not the reincarnated spirits of the Heike clan. They were something else. Something ancient and evil. Something that fed on human souls and took their forms.</p>

<p>She had found the heikegani horror.</p>

<p>And it had found her.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy loved crabs, she would read about them, draw them and would love going to the beach searching for them. It helped that her parents were Marine Biologists and would shift base every few years. She used to love going to search for crabs with her parents on Sundays. As she grew older, she would ride her bike to the beach and look for crabs and journal about them.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apocalypse</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/02/apocalypse.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apocalypse" /><published>2023-09-02T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-09-02T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/02/apocalypse</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/09/02/apocalypse.html"><![CDATA[<p>We tried everything, but it was imminent. The leaders were old, and instead of wisdom were full of ego. There was no way to calm the situation down.</p>

<p>The sirens started blaring, as I ordered all my subordinates to head towards the bunker. We had at best 5 minutes before the missiles hit our soil, and maybe 6 before ours would hit the ‘enemy’.</p>

<p>We always knew, it would only take one country to fire their missile and for the chain reaction to occur. The world map was showing lots of blips as I ran out of the room.</p>

<p>I had about three minutes, as I ran towards the bunkers. I hoped that my family was already inside, safe and sound. I prayed that they would forgive me for cutting it so close.</p>

<p>I had about a minute left as I reached the entrance and punched in the code. The door slid open and I dashed in, slamming it shut behind me. I heard a loud thud as the lock engaged. We were hopefully safe, for now. I looked around the room, and saw dozens of people huddled in the dimly lit space. Some of them were crying, some were praying, some were even staring blankly at the walls. I searched for my wife and kids, but I couldn’t find them. I called out my daughter’s name, everyone but my family stared back at me.</p>

<p>‘Where were they?’ I thought to myself. As I ran to the nearest monitor, I heard the first blast. I looked through the list of registered occupants and there were almost 50 names on the list… but none of them were mine or my family’s. How could this be? Did they go to another bunker? Had they been turned away? Had they been caught in the blast?</p>

<p>A surge of panic and anger coursed through me. I couldn’t think straight. Grabbing the nearest person, I shook him urgently. “Where are they?” I shouted, desperation in my voice. “Where are my wife and kids?”</p>

<p>The man’s face contorted with fear and confusion. He stammered, “Who are you? What are you talking about?”</p>

<p>I took a deep breath, my anxiety clawing at my chest. “I’m their husband and father,” I said, my voice trembling. “They were supposed to be here, but there names are not on the list. Please, I need to find them.” I let go of him and backed away.
The weight of a terrible mistake settled upon me like a suffocating shroud. I had mistakenly entered the wrong bunker, sealing my fate to die among strangers. My family, somewhere out there, their fate uncertain—alive or dead. Overwhelmed by despair, I sank to the bunker floor, burying my face in trembling hands. Uncontrollable sobs wracked my body as the world outside faced its apocalyptic demise.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We tried everything, but it was imminent. The leaders were old, and instead of wisdom were full of ego. There was no way to calm the situation down.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Superior</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/21/superior.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Superior" /><published>2023-08-21T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-21T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/21/superior</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/21/superior.html"><![CDATA[<p>Growing up a latch-key kid, he had to spend a lot of time on his own. While he liked playing video games, he could never spend too much time on it. What he really loved was reading, immersing in the stories, living vicariously through the characters, far away in their worlds. There were adventures and companionship, and as he lost track of time and reality, it was his own TARDIS.</p>

<p>One day, while walking back home, he saw a book lying on a bench. he thought maybe someone forgot it there. He picked up the book, and read the title “You &amp; I”, there was no cover design, or a name of the author. He was intrigued further. He decided to sit down and read it, while waiting for the owner to return and collect the book. He felt this way no one steals it, plus he gets to read a book too.</p>

<p>As he read a few pages,  he realized the book was quite different from any other he had ever read. He quickly flipped through the book and he was intrigued that there was no beginning, no chapters, and quite a few empty pages. He took a deep breath and started reading properly… The book seemed to have no plots, no dialogues, no descriptions. It was a book that had only words, someone’s hallucinating thought process just added there…</p>

<p>The words though flowed endlessly, without pause or punctuation. Strings of words that made no sense, but it somehow hypnotized him. Words that drew him in deeper and deeper, until he couldn’t stop reading. Words that surrounded him, enveloped him, drowned him.</p>

<p>He realized too late that he was trapped in the book, and that there was no way out. He realized too late that he was suffocating in the words, and that there was no air. He realized too late that he had reached a depth that wasn’t possible within a book, as his thoughts turned into words and filling empty pages.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up a latch-key kid, he had to spend a lot of time on his own. While he liked playing video games, he could never spend too much time on it. What he really loved was reading, immersing in the stories, living vicariously through the characters, far away in their worlds. There were adventures and companionship, and as he lost track of time and reality, it was his own TARDIS.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Depths</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/18/depths.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Depths" /><published>2023-08-18T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-18T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/18/depths</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/18/depths.html"><![CDATA[<p>Growing up a latch-key kid, he had to spend a lot of time on his own. While he liked playing video games, he could never spend too much time on it. What he really loved was reading, immersing in the stories, living vicariously through the characters, far away in their worlds. There were adventures and companionship, and as he lost track of time and reality, it was his own TARDIS.</p>

<p>One day, while walking back home, he saw a book lying on a bench. he thought maybe someone forgot it there. He picked up the book, and read the title “You &amp; I”, there was no cover design, or a name of the author. He was intrigued further. He decided to sit down and read it, while waiting for the owner to return and collect the book. He felt this way no one steals it, plus he gets to read a book too.</p>

<p>As he read a few pages,  he realized the book was quite different from any other he had ever read. He quickly flipped through the book and he was intrigued that there was no beginning, no chapters, and quite a few empty pages. He took a deep breath and started reading properly… The book seemed to have no plots, no dialogues, no descriptions. It was a book that had only words, someone’s hallucinating thought process just added there…</p>

<p>The words though flowed endlessly, without pause or punctuation. Strings of words that made no sense, but it somehow hypnotized him. Words that drew him in deeper and deeper, until he couldn’t stop reading. Words that surrounded him, enveloped him, drowned him.</p>

<p>He realized too late that he was trapped in the book, and that there was no way out. He realized too late that he was suffocating in the words, and that there was no air. He realized too late that he had reached a depth that wasn’t possible within a book, as his thoughts turned into words and filling empty pages.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up a latch-key kid, he had to spend a lot of time on his own. While he liked playing video games, he could never spend too much time on it. What he really loved was reading, immersing in the stories, living vicariously through the characters, far away in their worlds. There were adventures and companionship, and as he lost track of time and reality, it was his own TARDIS.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Violet</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/16/violet.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Violet" /><published>2023-08-16T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-16T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/16/violet</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/16/violet.html"><![CDATA[<p>“Penny for your thoughts…”, she looked up and said, “Mom, how did you and dad meet?”</p>

<p>Her mother, looked backed and smiled, “It was a long time ago, when online chat rooms used to be a big things for us teenagers. We ended up discussing a show in a city based chatroom.”</p>

<p>“Slowly, we started talking more often, we talked of books we liked and movies and music. We really liked talking to each other. It was months of this, before your dad asked to meet me. He said, ‘You know, it’s like I’ve known you forever.’, and when he said, that we should meet… I knew the perfect way to test out his proclamation…”</p>

<p>Her dad walks into the room mid sentence, and chimes, “She suggested we meet in one of the biggest park in our city, and all I knew was her onscreen name, and asked to meet her where her favorite flowers bloom.” She, looked back at her mom and saw her smile, “Well, since he ‘knew me since forever’, I didn’t see why he shouldn’t be able to guess my favorite flower”.</p>

<p>“So there I was, sitting in the grass, reading a book. I was quite nervous to meet someone from the internet… but I looked up to see a teenage boy holding a board with my screen name, and a bouquet of my favorite flowers.”</p>

<p>“And that’s why when he had you, we both knew, Violet would be the perfect name.”</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Penny for your thoughts…”, she looked up and said, “Mom, how did you and dad meet?”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cunning</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/15/cunning.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cunning" /><published>2023-08-15T17:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-15T17:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/15/cunning</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2023/08/15/cunning.html"><![CDATA[<p>Weeks have passed since she started working there. She sees him sitting inconspicuously, far enough that someone else wouldn’t notice, but, she was given a task. She isn’t sure if he has caught on, but she has always been a step ahead of everyone. “You gotta be, you know?” she says to herself. So during a busy afternoon, she goes to the back, carrying a brown paper bag.</p>

<p>He has been monitoring her for weeks; the client reached out to him months ago and told him when she’ll start working there. He regularly changed the car he has been using, parking in different spots, keeping an eye on the neighborhood. The client had given the date of “the accident,” and he needed to understand all possible patterns through the day to come up with a simple plan. He sees her enter the kitchen. He knows there’s an exit from back there, but he isn’t worried; his wife is keeping an eye out for their target, if she steps out. “Hey Anna, the target has gone to the kitchen. Keep an eye out for her.”, he speaks into the phone.</p>

<p>It has been longer than she would usually take. “Hey Anna, did she step out?” - “Negative,” he gets a quick reply.</p>

<p>He’s feeling a little restless waiting for her to return. He decides to step out and stretch his leg. As soon as he steps out of the car, an unexpected sensation courses through him—a searing prick on the nape of his neck. He looks back, the surroundings blur into a dizzying whirl as he falters… his gaze locking onto the figure of the killer. In that fateful moment, a haunting realization dawns in his eyes before his strength gives way. With one last, lingering look, he collapses, life slipping away.</p>

<p>She retrieves her phone as she leans in to assess his pulse, confirming the inevitable. She speaks into the device, her voice unwavering: “Hey Anna, it’s done.”</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weeks have passed since she started working there. She sees him sitting inconspicuously, far enough that someone else wouldn’t notice, but, she was given a task. She isn’t sure if he has caught on, but she has always been a step ahead of everyone. “You gotta be, you know?” she says to herself. So during a busy afternoon, she goes to the back, carrying a brown paper bag.]]></summary></entry></feed>