<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-10-28T23:03:31+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Short Stories</title><subtitle>This is a blog compiling all the stories from the prompts received on bluesky.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Bitcoin Blitz</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/24/BitcoinBlitz.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bitcoin Blitz" /><published>2024-08-24T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-24T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/24/BitcoinBlitz</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/24/BitcoinBlitz.html"><![CDATA[<p>Shreyan was a young man, enjoying his simple life, which also involved occasionally touching grass. He was a software engineer, content with his modest apartment and the gentle rhythm of his days.</p>

<p>One day he posted
“hi guys send some bitcoin to bc1qgmxv6u9s6amcmq2yu34fjrh9322ej4mksn53gz just for fun 🤗”</p>

<p>And the next morning, a notification from his cryptocurrency wallet jolted him awake.</p>

<p>Millions. Millions worth of bitcoins.
No explanation, no warning, just a windfall that defied logic. But the universe, it seemed, was not generous without a caveat. A cryptic message followed the transaction: “Spend 10% in the next 10 hours. No investments, no assets. Spend them on experiences only.”</p>

<p>–</p>

<p>Panic set in. Ten percent of what he received was still in millions. But what could one do with that kind of money in ten hours? The world was a vast, glittering bazaar of experiences, but to pick and choose in such haste was a daunting task.</p>

<p>A flight to the other side of the world seemed the most efficient use of time. Europe, with its ancient cities and vibrant cultures, promised a whirlwind of experiences. A private jet was booked, the fastest available.</p>

<p>In the heart of Europe, he stumbled upon an advertisement that made his jaw drop. A service offered the rental of fighter jets. The price tag was astronomical, a figure that would have made his pre-bitcoin self faint. But now, while it felt merely a rounding error, he realized it might help put a dent in the 10%.</p>

<p>–</p>

<p>Soaring through the sky, the clouds whipping past him, adrenaline coursing through his veins, Shreyan felt a sense of freedom he’d never known. He was a bird, a comet, a conqueror of the skies.</p>

<p>The world below shrank, transformed into a patchwork quilt of greens and blues. But as the jet crossed the infamous Bermuda Triangle, something strange happened. The world seemed to shimmer, to distort. A moment of disorientation, and then, nothing.</p>

<p>He fell. Fell through a void of blackness, a space devoid of time and gravity. And as the world spun into oblivion, a final thought crossed his mind: perhaps the universe had not been so generous after all.</p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3l2hgoj3jf72c" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreiaht7ryiseuqyxxupfav2makoj4obofe5mkwglb5poyljz3mnusxu"><p lang="en">Here you go @shreyanjain.net ^_^ 

you have been included~~~ 

#ShortStory #LetThereBeDeath<br /><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3l2hgoj3jf72c?ref_src=embed">[image or embed]</a></p>&mdash; The Spooky Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3l2hgoj3jf72c?ref_src=embed">Aug 24, 2024 at 3:44 PM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shreyan was a young man, enjoying his simple life, which also involved occasionally touching grass. He was a software engineer, content with his modest apartment and the gentle rhythm of his days.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Cosmic Slip</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/16/cosmicslip.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Cosmic Slip" /><published>2024-08-16T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-16T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/16/cosmicslip</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/16/cosmicslip.html"><![CDATA[<p>It was a rainy Tuesday afternoon when Conor stepped into the cavernous store. The fluorescent lights buzzed overhead, illuminating towering shelves stacked with industrial-sized ketchup bottles, family packs of toilet paper, and enough frozen pizza to feed a small army. Conor’s mission: to stock up on essentials for the impending apocalypse (or at least the next snowstorm).</p>

<p>As he rounded the corner near the dairy section, his cart laden with enough cheese to build a mozzarella fortress, Conor’s foot hit something slippery. His legs shot out from under him, and he executed a perfect split, arms flailing like a startled octopus. The culprit? A puddle of what appeared to be… pee pee. Yes, you read that right—pee pee. Conor’s face contorted in disgust as he tried to regain his balance.</p>

<p>But this was no ordinary puddle. As Conor struggled to stand, the universe hiccuped. The linoleum floor rippled like a disturbed pond, and the air crackled with otherworldly energy. Shoppers froze mid-reach for jumbo-sized cereal boxes, their eyes wide with terror.</p>

<p>Conor’s slip had torn a hole in the fabric of reality—a cosmic void that defied the laws of physics, common decency, and membership discounts. He felt himself being pulled toward it, his limbs elongating like taffy. The void whispered secrets in ancient tongues, promising forbidden knowledge and unlimited samples of artisanal hummus.</p>

<p>“Help!” Conor shouted, but his voice echoed strangely, as if it were bouncing off distant galaxies. The void yawned wider, revealing glimpses of eldritch horrors—tentacles, eyes, and teeth that defied geometry. One particularly polite horror even tipped its hat at him.</p>

<p>Conor’s life flashed before his eyes: the Excel spreadsheets, the failed attempts at sourdough baking, the unresolved tension with his neighbor’s cat. Was this how it all ended? Slipped on pee pee, sucked into the void, and devoured by beings beyond comprehension?</p>

<p>He had one chance. Conor reached into his pocket and pulled out his Costco membership card. With trembling hands, he swiped it through the void, hoping for a discount on existential dread. To his surprise, the void hiccuped again, and a cosmic receipt emerged. “Congratulations!” it read. “You’ve unlocked the ‘Eternal Abyss’ reward tier. Enjoy your infinite torment!”</p>

<p>And just like that, Conor ceased to exist. His atoms scattered across dimensions, his consciousness folded into a Möbius strip of despair. The eldritch horrors debated whether to rate his slip on Yelp.</p>

<p>As for the puddle of pee pee, it remained, a testament to the absurdity of existence. Costco management put up a caution sign: “Slippery When Eldritch.” And somewhere in the multiverse, Conor’s ghost muttered, “At least I got my money’s worth.”</p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3kzt76nvshl2i" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreifjuskdtmshsp2ftakcggimbjmvnhzjnxjqcp2flln7z6lu5t7bhu"><p lang="en">@conorvoice.com thank you for the support and here&#x27;s a special story for you :) 

#ShortStory #Eldritch #Horror adjacent.<br /><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kzt76nvshl2i?ref_src=embed">[image or embed]</a></p>&mdash; The Spooky Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kzt76nvshl2i?ref_src=embed">Aug 16, 2024 at 2:37 PM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a rainy Tuesday afternoon when Conor stepped into the cavernous store. The fluorescent lights buzzed overhead, illuminating towering shelves stacked with industrial-sized ketchup bottles, family packs of toilet paper, and enough frozen pizza to feed a small army. Conor’s mission: to stock up on essentials for the impending apocalypse (or at least the next snowstorm).]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Curious Case of Dr. Alkhadran’s Circus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/07/alkhadran.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Curious Case of Dr. Alkhadran’s Circus" /><published>2024-08-07T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-07T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/07/alkhadran</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/07/alkhadran.html"><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Dennis Hansen, the Head of Concept &amp; Content Development at the newly established Natural History Museum of NeoZurich Island, was a man of peculiar tastes. His office was adorned with ancient tomes, fossilized ammonites, and an Aldacabra giant tortoise. The latter, affectionately named “Aldo,” was his constant companion during late-night research sessions.</p>

<p>Dr. Hansen had a secret passion: rewilding. He dreamed of reintroducing long-extinct creatures to their natural habitats. His eyes sparkled when he spoke of woolly mammoths roaming the Swiss Alps or pterosaurs gliding over Lake Zurich. But his most fervent desire was to see Aldacabra tortoises once again lumbering across the island’s lush landscapes.</p>

<p>One fateful evening, while cataloging fossils from a recent excavation, Dr. Hansen stumbled upon an ancient vial. Its label, faded but legible, read: “Sample 497: Circusitis.” and below it some one had written “Possible use case: biostasis-reversal”.</p>

<p>Back in his office, he was showing the vial to Aldo, when suddenly a loud sound outside distracted Dr. Hansen and he dropped the vial. Little did he know his life was about to take a comical detour, as he inhaled a faint but musty scent.</p>

<p>Within days, Dr. Hansen felt an odd sensation—a tickling in his throat, a spring in his step. His skin took on a porcelain pallor, and his once-serious demeanor gave way to spontaneous laughter. He became the museum’s resident jester, entertaining visitors with pratfalls and balloon animals. Aldo watched from his enclosure, eyes wide with tortoise bewilderment.</p>

<p>As weeks turned into months, the metamorphosis accelerated. Dr. Hansen sprouted a bulbous red nose and his limbs stretched to absurd proportions. His office, once a sanctuary of knowledge, transformed into a chaotic circus tent.</p>

<p>One moonlit night, Dr. Hansen followed an inexplicable urge. He squeezed into a tiny clown car parked outside the museum—a car that turned out to be impossibly spacious from the inside. To his surprise, it accommodated not only him but also twenty-nine other clowns. They honked horns, juggled rubber chickens, and squeezed into improbable positions.</p>

<p>The car sped down Neo-Zurich Island’s winding roads, its tires emitting a comical squeak. Dr. Hansen laughed until tears streamed down his painted cheeks. The other clowns—each with their own peculiarities—joined the cacophony. There was Professor Chuckles, the astrophysicist-turned-pie-thrower, and Trixie the Trapeze Artist, who balanced atop the car’s roof.</p>

<p>But fate had a cruel twist. As they careened toward the island’s cliffs, Dr. Hansen realized the car’s brakes were mere rubber chickens. Panic swept through the clown car. They swerved, spun, and somersaulted, their painted faces contorting in terror. The car teetered on the edge, and Dr. Hansen clung to Aldo’s miniature replica, praying for salvation.</p>

<p>With a final, absurd twist, the car plummeted into the abyss. The sea swallowed them whole, and the laughter turned to silence. Neo-Zurich Island mourned its lost clowns—their oversized shoes washing ashore like forgotten relics.</p>

<p>And so,  Dr. Hansen , the biologist-turned-buffoon, met his end. His legacy? A cautionary tale whispered among museum staff: “Beware the Circusitis Virus, for it turns scholars into jesters and sends them hurtling toward absurdity.”</p>

<p>As for Aldo, the giant tortoise? Some say he still roams the island, occasionally pausing to perform a clumsy pirouette. Perhaps he remembers Dr. Hansen —the man who dared to dream of rewilding, even if it meant becoming a clown.</p>

<p>And so, dear reader, the next time you visit Neo-Zurich Island, spare a thought for the lost souls who once squeezed into that ill-fated clown car. Their laughter echoes through the fossil-strewn cliffs, a reminder that even in tragedy, there’s a touch of whimsy.</p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3kz5grnusmk2a" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreielvl7ufjlhazxidm6eazhee3vgw5jp2l4rbnacuvs2zo64k6k72y"><p lang="en">Hi @dennish.bsky.social ~~ 

Thank you for for the support, and here&#x27;s a special story for you, as a thank you as well. 

(I think you might enjoy some of the easter eggs more than others) 

#ShortStory<br /><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kz5grnusmk2a?ref_src=embed">[image or embed]</a></p>&mdash; The Spooky Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kz5grnusmk2a?ref_src=embed">Aug 7, 2024 at 10:54 PM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Dennis Hansen, the Head of Concept &amp; Content Development at the newly established Natural History Museum of NeoZurich Island, was a man of peculiar tastes. His office was adorned with ancient tomes, fossilized ammonites, and an Aldacabra giant tortoise. The latter, affectionately named “Aldo,” was his constant companion during late-night research sessions.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Skydiving to Oblivion</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/05/skydiving.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Skydiving to Oblivion" /><published>2024-08-05T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-05T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/05/skydiving</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/05/skydiving.html"><![CDATA[<p>Gilbertine was not an adrenaline junkie. She preferred the quiet comfort of her armchair embroidering on a weekend, to the thrill of anything remotely resembling excitement. But her best friend, a whirlwind of energy and impulsiveness, had convinced her that a tandem skydive would be a “once-in-a-lifetime experience.” Gilbertine had envisioned the “experience” as a leisurely picnic with Bollywood movies being projected on a big screen… not plummeting towards Earth at terminal velocity.</p>

<p>As the plane climbed, Gilbertine’s grip on the instructor’s harness tightened. The ground, once a familiar patchwork quilt, now resembled a menacing abyss. The moment of truth arrived sooner than she’d liked. With a shove that felt like a betrayal, she was plummeting towards the ground.</p>

<p>The parachute didn’t open.</p>

<p>A scream, ripped from her throat as the wind whipped past her face. Gilbertine’s last thought, a bizarrely calm one considering her situation, was, “Well, this is going to be a really expensive funeral.”</p>

<p>As fear, pure and unadulterated, consumed her. It was in that moment of abject terror that an ancient, cosmic entity, bored beyond comprehension, noticed.</p>

<p>In the cosmic void, an ancient, bored entity was idly flipping through dimensions. Its existence was a monotonous loop of nothingness until it was drawn to the intense, raw fear emanating from Earth. Curiosity piqued, it reached out to investigate.</p>

<p>Before Gilbertine could even process the horror of her situation, a tendril of cosmic evil reached out. It wasn’t drawn to her physical form, but to the essence of her terror.</p>

<p>And then it sneezed.</p>

<p>Not just any sneeze. This was a cosmic sneeze, a cataclysmic event that ripped a hole in the fabric of reality. Through this breach, a slimy, tendril-like substance oozed into our world. Tiny at first, it began to grow at an alarming rate, its appetite insatiable.</p>

<p>And so, Gilbertine, the woman who preferred tea to turbulence, became the unwitting harbinger of cosmic doom. It was, in the grand scheme of things, a truly awful way to spend an afternoon.</p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3kyvk6ibxyg23" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreiacnnl6jk4ceyvdfzlriorqbztccjhh7fbbvpqp6t6lag4272lfni"><p lang="en">Hey @gilbertine.bsky.social wrote something as a thank you for all the support ^_^ 

(Hope you enjoy it) 

#ShortStory<br /><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kyvk6ibxyg23?ref_src=embed">[image or embed]</a></p>&mdash; The Spooky Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kyvk6ibxyg23?ref_src=embed">Aug 4, 2024 at 7:34 PM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gilbertine was not an adrenaline junkie. She preferred the quiet comfort of her armchair embroidering on a weekend, to the thrill of anything remotely resembling excitement. But her best friend, a whirlwind of energy and impulsiveness, had convinced her that a tandem skydive would be a “once-in-a-lifetime experience.” Gilbertine had envisioned the “experience” as a leisurely picnic with Bollywood movies being projected on a big screen… not plummeting towards Earth at terminal velocity.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Death by Laughter (or Humor Imbalance)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/04/humorimbalance.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Death by Laughter (or Humor Imbalance)" /><published>2024-08-04T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-04T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/04/humorimbalance</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/04/humorimbalance.html"><![CDATA[<p>Trish wasn’t your average comedy club attendee. A staunch believer in the ancient Greek theory of humors, she was convinced that laughter was a direct assault on the delicate balance of her bodily fluids. She’d tried to explain this to her friends, but they’d just rolled their eyes and tell her to “get a life”.</p>

<p>One evening, determined to prove her point, Trish dragged her skeptical best friend, Gertrude, to a stand-up comedy show. The lanky comedian, Gary, regaled the audience with tales of disastrous first dates.</p>

<p>Trish teetered on the edge. Each joke felt like a tiny dagger, chipping away at her carefully maintained equilibrium. a desperate attempt to counteract the rising tide of mirth. But Gary’s punchline about a date’s pet iguana pushed her over the edge.</p>

<p>The audience erupted in laughter. Trish turned an odd shade of green, eyes rolling back as she gracefully collapsed from her seat. Silence followed, then nervous chuckles. Gary, ever the pro, paused for a dramatic beat before announcing, “Well, that’s a new one.”</p>

<p>While paramedics whisked Trish away, “I warned you about laughter,” she muttered, as Gertrude shook her head.</p>

<p>The coroner’s report would later cite “acute humor imbalance” as the cause of death. It was a medical mystery that would baffle doctors for years to come. And so, Mildred became a legend, the woman who died laughing. Or, as some would say, a victim of her own deeply held beliefs.</p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3kysf3fd66v2v" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreiff43j3hllzeiy2ewg5w7eq4i23ggo37lrypvrgs72j2qpwoqzvfi"><p lang="en">Hey 
@trishyb.bsky.social, while I still sort out the postcard situation, here&#x27;s something as a thank you for the support :)

#ShortStory<br /><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kysf3fd66v2v?ref_src=embed">[image or embed]</a></p>&mdash; The Spooky Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kysf3fd66v2v?ref_src=embed">Aug 3, 2024 at 1:24 PM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trish wasn’t your average comedy club attendee. A staunch believer in the ancient Greek theory of humors, she was convinced that laughter was a direct assault on the delicate balance of her bodily fluids. She’d tried to explain this to her friends, but they’d just rolled their eyes and tell her to “get a life”.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">E-book and the Next set of stories</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/03/ebook01.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="E-book and the Next set of stories" /><published>2024-08-03T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-08-03T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/03/ebook01</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deathclock/2024/08/03/ebook01.html"><![CDATA[<p>These short stories, started a year back in August of 2023, when I first asked Bluesky users to share a prompt. While my original idea was to write 100-200 word stories some of the stories are way longer. I don’t think I ever managed to write something that short.</p>

<p>Last month I decided to compile these stories into an E-book and share with friends, mutuals and followers across social media. As you know I mostly share the stories as screengrab with alt-text on bsky, apart from sharing them on this site - I felt it might be nicer to have a format that people can read on their e-reader as well.</p>

<p>So if you’d like to download the book. <a href="https://ko-fi.com/s/d33c50d04d">Check out this Ko-fi link</a>.</p>

<p>p.s. the e-book contains three extra stories that are not available on the website.</p>

<p><br />
<br /></p>

<p>So what’s next?</p>

<p>If you’ve been on bluesky for a while, you know about the labellers. While the original design behind this is to create a 3rd party moderation layer, certain labellers are creating some fun projects with these. One of the fun ones is called <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:fqfzpua2rp5io5nmxcixvdvm">The Cave of Trophonius</a> which has labelled every active account with how the user will meet their demise.</p>

<p>So I’ve decided to start using these as prompt to write stories. I will start sharing the stories on this site as well in the near future, but currently you can check the stories on bluesky.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3kyr7qa7dcs2w" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreiatm32bhvl7sqgnyabm3nwrt6febxx6zdjv2f4lag26gmhk25a264"><p lang="en">I&#x27;m going to start using @oracle.posters.rip label to write a few stories for mutuals. 

🙃🙃🙃</p>&mdash; The 🟦 Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kyr7qa7dcs2w?ref_src=embed">Aug 3, 2024 at 2:16 AM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="deathclock" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[These short stories, started a year back in August of 2023, when I first asked Bluesky users to share a prompt. While my original idea was to write 100-200 word stories some of the stories are way longer. I don’t think I ever managed to write something that short.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Petrichor</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/07/22/petrichor.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Petrichor" /><published>2024-07-22T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-07-22T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/07/22/petrichor</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/07/22/petrichor.html"><![CDATA[<p>In the heart of the desolate city of Xericus, where the sun’s relentless gaze had scorched the cobblestone streets for eight decades, an eerie silence hung heavy. The once bustling marketplace now lay abandoned, its stalls covered in a thick layer of dust. The townspeople moved like shadows, their eyes hollow, their souls parched.</p>

<p>The city’s survival depended on a forbidden art—the Rain-weavers. These enigmatic figures, cloaked in tattered robes, gathered at the edge of the city each dawn. With ancient chants and cryptic gestures, they wove illusions of raindrops, conjuring mirages that shimmered in the air. The townsfolk watched, desperate for relief, as the ephemeral droplets evaporated before touching the ground.</p>

<p>Among them was Evelyn, the oldest resident. Her memory stretched back to the last true rain, when she was a child.  But as the years passed, the memory faded, replaced by the sterile illusion of Rain-weaver magic.</p>

<p>One sweltering afternoon, as the sun blazed mercilessly, Evelyn shuffled to the city’s edge. The Rain-weavers were at work, their hands weaving invisible threads. But today felt different. Dark clouds gathered overhead, and the air crackled with anticipation. The townspeople whispered, their voices trembling. They’d only read about clouds, and thunderstorm, and never seen one. They weren’t sure if this was a new illusion the Rain-weavers had created.</p>

<p>Then it happened—the first genuine raindrop in eight decades. It splashed onto Evelyn’s wrinkled hand, and she gasped. The sensation was both alien and familiar—the cool touch of water, and instantly she was hit with the earthy fragrance. Tears welled in her eyes as she remembered her childhood, playing in puddles, laughing with friends.</p>

<p>Evelyn sat herself on a weathered bench, raindrops patterning her thin shawl.</p>

<p>She closed her eyes, allowing the memories to flood back. She recalled her mother’s voice, singing lullabies during storms, and her father’s laughter as they danced in the rain.</p>

<p>Beside her, a Rain-weaver faltered. The illusion wavered, revealing the truth —the sky wept genuine tears. The townspeople rejoiced, but Evelyn remained still.</p>

<p>Petrichor—the word echoed in her mind, resurrected from oblivion.</p>

<p>She whispered to the rain, her voice lost in the downpour, “Thank you for remembering my favorite word.” The intoxicating scent of wet earth seeped into her very bones.</p>

<p>And as the city drank its first true rain, Evelyn’s memories flowed like rivulets, carving new channels in her soul. She vowed to preserve the petrichor, to pass it down to the next generation. For in that fleeting moment, amidst eldritch magic and forgotten words, she found solace—a fragile hope that Xericus might yet thrive, nourished by both rain and memory.</p>

<blockquote class="bluesky-embed" data-bluesky-uri="at://did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/app.bsky.feed.post/3kxv6d2gotn2d" data-bluesky-cid="bafyreif3zmyn6lcz3rs53jtwbdwdd3y2qgaa6g56wbcaw727tob2h3yyti"><p lang="en">Petrichor. 

cc: @cookieduh.xyz 

#ShortStory  

If you&#x27;d like to read it on web, here you go: ss.lucidillusions.in/short/story/...<br /><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kxv6d2gotn2d?ref_src=embed">[image or embed]</a></p>&mdash; The 🟦 Doctor (<a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7?ref_src=embed">@lucidillusions.in</a>) <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/did:plc:36h6ttx2g23zqr4accilbvo7/post/3kxv6d2gotn2d?ref_src=embed">Jul 22, 2024 at 10:36 PM</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://embed.bsky.app/static/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the heart of the desolate city of Xericus, where the sun’s relentless gaze had scorched the cobblestone streets for eight decades, an eerie silence hung heavy. The once bustling marketplace now lay abandoned, its stalls covered in a thick layer of dust. The townspeople moved like shadows, their eyes hollow, their souls parched.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Valence</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/06/28/valence.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Valence" /><published>2024-06-28T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-06-28T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/06/28/valence</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/06/28/valence.html"><![CDATA[<p>Within the cavernous belly of the defunct power plant, Dr. Evelyn Kessler stood before the control panel. Dust motes danced in the shaft of her flashlight, illuminating a scene of decay.  The air, heavy with the metallic tang of rust, held a different kind of weight too - the weight of a forgotten dream. Her eyes, once bright with scientific curiosity, were now haunted—etched with the knowledge that could unravel the world.</p>

<p>The valence reactor, a relic from a forgotten era, hummed ominously. Its core pulsed with energy, each electron transition felt less controlled and more like a heartbeat on the verge of arrhythmia. Dr. Kessler had discovered the truth—the reason behind inexplicable meltdowns, the whispers of malevolence that echoed through the corridors.</p>

<p>Her trembling fingers trailed across the equations scrawled on the grimy chalkboard, desperately connecting the dots that stretched across space and time.</p>

<p>The valence transitions weren’t mere physics; they were conduits for something ancient and hungry. With every tiny leap, an unseen force stirred—a malefic presence that fed on fear, anger, and despair.</p>

<p>The Chernobyl disaster—the world had blamed it on human error, but Dr. Kessler knew better, now. The reactor’s valence cascade had torn a rift, allowing the malevolence to seep through. The technicians, unsuspecting, had become vessels for its wrath. The screams of the dying that echoed in her nightmares.</p>

<p>Now, in this forsaken place, she sought answers. The control rods trembled as she adjusted them, trying to stabilize the reactor. But the malevolence resisted—a sentient force that defied containment. It whispered promises of forbidden knowledge, of dominion over reality itself.</p>

<p>Dr. Kessler’s colleagues had vanished one by one. Their eyes glazed, mouths spouting gibberish—the malevolence claimed them. She had glimpsed its form—an eldritch geometry that twisted sanity. It hungered for release, and the valence transitions were its gateway.</p>

<p>As midnight approached, the reactor’s glow intensified. Dr. Kessler hesitated. She could shut it down, seal the rift forever. But the malevolence whispered in her mind, promising answers to questions she hadn’t dared ask. The world’s suffering, the weight of existence—could she bear it alone?</p>

<p>She stepped closer, her breath ragged. The valence cascade surged, and the room quaked. Shadows writhed, coalescing into tendrils that reached for her. The equations burned in her vision—the key to understanding, the price of damnation.</p>

<p>And then, with a scream that echoed through time, Dr. Kessler plunged her hand into the reactor core. The malevolence surged, engulfing her. She glimpsed other worlds—twisted, broken—where civilizations crumbled under its influence. It hungered for chaos, entropy, oblivion.</p>

<p>The reactor exploded, a blinding flash that consumed everything. Dr. Kessler became one with the malevolence, her consciousness fracturing across dimensions. She whispered secrets to the void, her voice carried on cosmic winds.</p>

<p>The world mourned the loss of the brilliant scientist. They blamed it on a reactor malfunction, never suspecting the eldritch truth. But sometimes, in the dead of night, a flicker of malevolence stirs—a reminder that evil isn’t always born of human hearts.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the cavernous belly of the defunct power plant, Dr. Evelyn Kessler stood before the control panel. Dust motes danced in the shaft of her flashlight, illuminating a scene of decay. The air, heavy with the metallic tang of rust, held a different kind of weight too - the weight of a forgotten dream. Her eyes, once bright with scientific curiosity, were now haunted—etched with the knowledge that could unravel the world.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Booka</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/05/18/booka.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Booka" /><published>2024-05-18T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-05-18T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/05/18/booka</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/05/18/booka.html"><![CDATA[<p>Once upon a time, on the edge of a bustling town, in a cozy little house, there lived a young girl named Tasha. She had no friends, but she had a pet, a very unusual pet - a cardboard box she’d named Booka. Unlike any ordinary box, Booka was magical and could transform to anything Tasha imagined. Every afternoon, the two of them would embark on the most wondrous adventures one could dream of.</p>

<p>One early Sunday morning, Tasha and Booka decided to explore the garden in their backyard, a place she called the “Jungle of the Giants”. Tasha’s heart pounded with excitement for their quest to find the legendary Golden Apple. Booka, usually sturdy and dependable, started to vibrate with Tasha’s energy, transforming into a sturdy safari jeep. Tasha, donning her explorer’s hat, took the wheel.</p>

<p>The garden was alive with the buzz off bees and the flutter of butterflies. Tasha steered Booka through the tall grass, which, to her, felt like towering trees of a dense forest. Thus began the quest to find the Golden Apple, said to be guarded by the Great Garden Gnome.</p>

<p>As the ventured deeper, they encountered a maze of sunflowers, each bloom as big as Booka. After a series of lefts and rights they found themselves at the heart of the maze. They had reached a small pond, shimmering under the sun. In the middle of the pond, on a lily pad, sat the Great Garden Gnome - a kindly old figure wearing a red pointy hat. He spoke in riddles and rhymes, challenging Tasha to a game of wit. If Tasha could answer all of his riddles, the path to the Golden Apple would be revealed.</p>

<p>With Booka’s whispers of encouragement as well as some help, Tasha solved the riddles one by one. Pleased, the Great Garden Gnome pointed to a hidden path lined withe daisies that led to a mythical apple tree. It’s branches heavy with fruits - and among them hung the Golden Apple, shimmering with a light of its own.</p>

<p>Tasha reached out and plucked the apple, and as she did, the garden burst into a symphony of colors and sounds. With their mission complete, Tasha and Booka returned home, the Golden Apple in hand. She knew that tomorrow would bring another adventure, but for now, they rested, basking in the joy of their jungle expedition - waiting for Tasha’s mother to finish baking her favorite apple pie.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time, on the edge of a bustling town, in a cozy little house, there lived a young girl named Tasha. She had no friends, but she had a pet, a very unusual pet - a cardboard box she’d named Booka. Unlike any ordinary box, Booka was magical and could transform to anything Tasha imagined. Every afternoon, the two of them would embark on the most wondrous adventures one could dream of.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lacunar</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/02/24/lacunar.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lacunar" /><published>2024-02-24T18:39:03+05:30</published><updated>2024-02-24T18:39:03+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/02/24/lacunar</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/short/story/2024/02/24/lacunar.html"><![CDATA[<p>In the heart of our vibrant city, amidst its neon-lit streets and towering buildings, was the research center. My colleague, Dr. Maya, a woman whose passion mirrored the city’s vibrant energy, was on the brink of a groundbreaking discovery related to the ‘Lacunar Anomaly Syndrome’. The anomaly, characterized by mysterious micro-voids in the brain tissues had sent ripples through the scientific community, placing us at the epicenter of this paradigm shift.</p>

<p>It all began a month ago with Mr. Kapoor, a seemingly ordinary middle-aged man who entered the sterile confines of our facility. We had no idea of the extraordinary anomaly lurking within him. What appeared initially like a severe case of sleep paralysis – characterized by the inability to move or speak despite being awake – lacked the expected telltale signs in Mr. Kapoor’s brainwaves. A man known for his gregarious nature, he now lay frozen, unable to even grunt in response to his growing discomfort.</p>

<p>A recent, ultra-high-resolution MRI scan revealed a startling discovery: micro-voids, but unlike any we had ever seen. These weren’t mere empty spaces; they seemed to be actively affecting the machine itself. Multiple scans, meticulously compared by Dr. Maya, unveiled an even more unsettling truth – the anomalies were shifting, pulsating in a seemingly rhythmic pattern, as if trying to transmit a message through their shifting shapes. It felt like a chilling revelation - hinting at a deeper mystery, a secret buried within the very core of existence.</p>

<p>Dr. Maya knew this was no ordinary case of sleep paralysis. This was the beginning of something far more profound, and potentially terrifying.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short" /><category term="story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the heart of our vibrant city, amidst its neon-lit streets and towering buildings, was the research center. My colleague, Dr. Maya, a woman whose passion mirrored the city’s vibrant energy, was on the brink of a groundbreaking discovery related to the ‘Lacunar Anomaly Syndrome’. The anomaly, characterized by mysterious micro-voids in the brain tissues had sent ripples through the scientific community, placing us at the epicenter of this paradigm shift.]]></summary></entry></feed>